{
    "id": "d963c2bac7ce4d7dbd7a1b935b05563a",
    "title": "Rewrite Without Get",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I (got) three hundred dollars last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "acquired",
                "gathered",
                "earned"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "16600b2d6a2b4bf9a2d5eeec805ece58"
        },
        {
            "question": "I (got) a letter from my mother this morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "earned",
                "received",
                "acquired"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd0c25083b334f7ea63f90de85969034"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you come and (get) me from the station when I arrive?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "fetch",
                "take"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "caae1164e02c4d229b23dbeec45f8477"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didnâ€™t (get) the joke.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "acquire",
                "find",
                "understand"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "28ca82247f304e6786da937e8439de8f"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the first half, the striker (got) a goal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "earned",
                "collected",
                "scored"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6a02ab423ab34c73b3d0a00123ab8156"
        },
        {
            "question": "While studying in Sydney, Rahul (got) a strong Australian accent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gathered",
                "earned",
                "acquired"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd710736559a4b169d08bdfeb8be9807"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother (got) the child to drink some of the milk.",
            "description": "After made the infinitive is used without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "coaxed",
                "fetched",
                "made"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c6c52b080934272a809bd70f059e4b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "During the trip, many children (got) ill.",
            "description": "Either fell or became is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "fell",
                "became",
                "turned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3b607dee10c0487aba443a2438acdcf4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Luckily we (got) the last bus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caught",
                "gained",
                "collected"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5e45f4f1bc5240888b41781bf5af56fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "They (got) a stay from the High Court.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "earned",
                "collected",
                "obtained"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7ecf206fdf6943e489ad532c8ca2aca8"
        }
    ]
}